{
    "subject": "resource/Sebastian_Kehl",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:2006_FIFA_World_Cup_players",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Sebastian Kehl is 2006 FIFA World Cup players.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8988762497901917,
            "question": "Did Sebastian Kehl win the FIFA World Cup in 2006?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7744331359863281,
            "question": "In what year did Sebastian Kehl participate in the FIFA World Cup?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7078181505203247,
            "question": "Who is Sebastian Kehl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6022582054138184,
            "question": "What position did Sebastian Kehl likely play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5932382345199585,
            "question": "What major sporting event is Sebastian Kehl associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5774655342102051,
            "question": "Is Sebastian Kehl a well-known footballer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.492858350276947,
            "question": "What is the significance of the 2006 FIFA World Cup?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44855910539627075,
            "question": "Was Sebastian Kehl part of a national team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3847269117832184,
            "question": "Can you name other players from the 2006 FIFA World Cup?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3531278967857361,
            "question": "Where was the 2006 FIFA World Cup held?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Sebastian Kehl is 2006 FIFA World Cup players.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2037_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name other players from the 2006 FIFA World Cup?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2037_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Sebastian Kehl part of a national team?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2037_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of the 2006 FIFA World Cup?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2037_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2037_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2037_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2037_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2037_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2037_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2037_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2037_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2037_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2037_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2037_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n**Explanation:**\n\nThe provided text documents state that Sebastian Kehl was called up to the German national team by J\u00fcrgen Klinsmann for the 2006 World Cup in Germany, and the German team won the World Cup on June 30, 2006.  This indicates that Sebastian Kehl was part of the 2006 FIFA World Cup players. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Sebastian Kehl's participation in the 2006 FIFA World Cup, supporting the statement that he was a player for the German national team during the 2006 FIFA World Cup."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Sebastian Kehl was part of the German national team for the 2006 World Cup, but he did not win the tournament. They lost in the semi-finals and won the third place game instead.",
            "category": 1
        }
    }
}